Gregório Benatti

Email: gregoriobenatti@gmail.com

Skype: gregoriobenatti Mobile: +358 41 479 4089

https://gregoriobenatti.github.io

- Profile Summary -

Full Stack Software Engineer with 10 years of programming experience. 3 years of mobile game development experience and 15+ games released. Experience with back-end, front-end, mobile app and game programming. Speaks English (advanced) and Brazilian Portuguese (native).

- Education -

Bachelor in Analysis and System Development

FATEC – Technology University of São Paulo | 2016 - 2018 (dropped out), São José dos Campos, SP.

Bachelor in Programming and Database Management

FATEC - Technology University of São Paulo | 2011 - 2016 (dropped out), São José dos Campos, SP.

High School Education - Technical Computing Formation

ETEP – Everardo Passos Technical School | 2004 - 2006, São José dos Campos, SP.

- Technical Strengths -

Java, Objective-C, Python, Lua, Groovy, Shell script, ActionScript 3, C++, C#, Unity3D, Godot Engine, CoronaSDK, GIT, Mac OS X, Unix/Linux, Oracle, PostgreSQL, iOS, Android, Agile Methodology.

- Professional Experience -

Critical Force | January 2018 - Present, Kajaani/Finland

Senior DevOps Engineer

Senior DevOps Engineer working on Continuous Integration systems, test automation and internal tools for game developers.

Working with: AWS, Jenkins, Groovy, Python, GIT, C#, Unity3D, iOS, Android, Agile.

Aguiris Game Studio | Mar 2017 - Oct 2017, Porto Alegre/Brazil

Software Engineer

As a Software Engineer on Game Client using Unity3D and C# as a main development tool, I work developing new game features, fixing bugs, design new system, profiling to find and

understand our game limits and help to improve the code. I also work with TDD, automate tests on devices and the continuous integration system, designing and creating solutions for tests, automation and continuous builds delivery for a NDA mobile multiplayer game.

Working with: Unity3D, C#, TDD, device tests automation, CI, Jenkins, shell script, python, git.

OnSet Tecnologia/Johnson & Johnson | August 2016 - February 2017, São José dos Campos/Brazil Business Intelligence Consultant

Developing and support the Ingestion framework, composed of several components like connectors, build tools, job managers and ingestion tools.

Working with: Cloudera Platform, AWS, EC2, Jenkins, shell script, python, IntelliJ, git, SQL.

Tapps Games | August 2014 - August 2016, São Paulo/Brazil Game Developer/Tools Programmer

Development of mobile games based on CoronaSDK, coding in Lua. Support all released games, fixing bugs and create new features (game updates).

Member of production team, developing of tools to improve quality, speed and support to the development team, working with native code for Android and iOS and making performance improvements to ensure the quality of the game.

Working with: Lua, CoronaSDK, Python, Android, iOS, Windows Phone, GIT, Jenkins.

Ericsson Telecommunications | June 2013 - July 2014, São José dos Campos/Brazil Software Developer

Development of Java code for an ERP and a CMS to telecom industry. Using development techniques like Continuous Integration, TDD, unit tests, pair programming, Scrum Agile methodology to guarantee code quality.

Working with: Java, JUnit, JSP, Eclipse IDE, Apache Tomcat, Oracle, GIT, Jenkins, Unix.

Touch Tecnologia | December 2011 - May 2013, São José dos Campos/Brazil Internship as Software Developer

Development of Java code for a scheduler web application to healthcare industry. Using development techniques like Continuous Integration, TDD, unit tests, pair programming, Scrum Agile methodology and web solutions for interfaces and usability.

Working with: Java, JUnit, JSP, Eclipse IDE, Apache Tomcat, Oragle, PostgreSQL, Maven, GIT, Hudson, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Ubuntu Linux.